http://www.ingles-markets.com/corporate/cg3/policies/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Choose or Change Homestore
Show menu
The Ingles AdvantageAdvantage CardAdvantage Card FAQAdvantageMail Weekly EmailAdvantageMailAdvantageMail FAQEducationTools for SchoolsCouponsPrint at Home CouponsCoupon PolicyWeekly AdsFlyer ViewScreen Reader CompatibleMobile/Grid View PharmacyFlu VaccinationsPharmacy Online RefillsPharmacy InfoPharmacy SurveyPharmacy CareersIn-Store VaccinationsNondiscrimination NoticeNotice of Privacy PracticesDietitianAbout LeahSubmit a QuestionPublic SpeakingAsk Leah!Nutrition BlogNutritionWhat is rBGHDiabetes InfoGluten-Free StoresGluten-Free ListGMOsTrans FatsBakery InfoDeli InfoOrganicFood InfoAlertsIngles TableRecipesBakeryCakes and CookiesWedding CakesDeliHoliday DinnersDeli Party TraysDeli CateringGiftsGift CardsDepartmentsBakeryBeer and WineDeliFloralFrozenGas ExpressGroceryMeatPharmacyProduceVideoCareerPharmacy CareersCorporate CareersDistribution Center CareersStore CareersLocationsStore Locations and InfoSelect Your Home StoreContact InglesContact InformationComments and SuggestionsHelpContact WebmasterRequest Investor PacketInvestor QuestionsStarbucksCareers ContactSocial MediaFacebookTwitterPinterestInstagramYouTubeInglesAll About InglesCareersCode of EthicsDiversity and Inclusion StatementSustainabilityAnimal WelfareDistributionMilkcoPress ReleasesSuppliersInvestorInvestor Packet RequestInvestor QuestionsRelated Party PolicyFinancial Press ReleasesAudit Committee CharterProxy StatementCommunitySustainabilityFund RaisingCommunity GivingPoliciesCoupon PolicyOnline Privacy Policy StatementAccessibility PolicyTerms and ConditionsSEC FilingsSEC All ReportsSEC Ownership ReportsSEC XBRL Files
Savings
The Ingles AdvantageAdvantage CardAdvantage Card FAQAdvantageMail Weekly EmailAdvantageMailAdvantageMail FAQEducationTools for SchoolsEducation SeparatorCouponsPrint at Home CouponsCoupon Policy
Weekly Ads
Weekly AdsFlyer ViewScreen Reader CompatibleMobile/Grid View
Pharmacy
PharmacyFlu VaccinationsPharmacy Online RefillsPharmacy InfoPharmacy SurveyPharmacy CareersIn-Store VaccinationsNondiscrimination NoticeNotice of Privacy PracticesPharmacy Image
Wellness
DietitianAbout LeahSubmit a QuestionPublic SpeakingAsk Leah!Nutrition BlogNutritionWhat is rBGHDiabetes InfoGluten-Free StoresGluten-Free ListGMOsTrans FatsBakery InfoDeli InfoOrganicFood InfoAlertsIngles TableRecipes
Inside Ingles
BakeryCakes and CookiesWedding CakesDeliHoliday DinnersDeli Party TraysDeli CateringGiftsGift CardsDepartmentsBakeryBeer and WineDeliFloralFrozenGas ExpressGroceryMeatPharmacyProduceVideoCareerPharmacy CareersCorporate CareersDistribution Center CareersStore CareersLocationsStore Locations and InfoSelect Your Home Store
Talk To Us
Contact InglesContact InformationComments and SuggestionsHelpContact WebmasterRequest Investor PacketInvestor QuestionsStarbucksCareers ContactSocial Media Facebook Twitter Pinterest Instagram YouTube
Corporate
InglesAll About InglesCareersCode of EthicsDiversity and Inclusion StatementSustainabilityAnimal WelfareDistributionMilkcoPress ReleasesSuppliersInvestorInvestor Packet RequestInvestor QuestionsRelated Party PolicyFinancial Press ReleasesAudit Committee CharterProxy StatementCommunitySustainabilityFund RaisingCommunity GivingPoliciesCoupon PolicyOnline Privacy Policy StatementAccessibility PolicyTerms and ConditionsSEC FilingsSEC All ReportsSEC Ownership ReportsSEC XBRL Files
Careers
Close ×
Keep up-to-date with your local Ingles Market, store specials and savings, please select your home store
State
Select a State:
Alabama
Georgia
North Carolina
South Carolina
Tennessee
Virginia
Submit
Online Privacy Statement
This is the web site of Ingles Markets, Inc.
Our postal address isPost Office Box 6676Asheville, NC 28816(828) 669-2941
This privacy statement covers the site www.ingles-markets.com. Because Ingles Markets, Inc wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, we have agreed to disclose our Web site information practices.
What personally identifiable information Ingles Markets, Inc collects.
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
What organization collects the information.
How Ingles Markets, Inc uses the information.
With whom Ingles Markets, Inc may share user information.
What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Ingles Markets, Inc control.
How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
What We CollectFor each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain and IP address.
We collect only the domain name and IP address, browser/operating system specs, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail or online contact forms, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact our Customer Service department by using our online Contact Form, calling, or writing us at the address above.
Information Collection and Use
Information CollectionIngles Markets, Inc collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site:
OrderWe request information from the user on our bakery, deli and gift card order forms. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, phone, and shipping address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user. We collect your ip address with each order ito help facilitate any order problems, to review any orders that may have been accidently sent multiple times or as a reference if the form has been abused.
ContactWe request information from the user on our Customer Service Contact and Contact The Webmaster forms. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and location). This information is used for contact purposes and to resolve any complaints, comments, or questions the user contacted us with.
Information Packet RequestWe request information from the user on our Information Packet Request form. A user must provide contact information so that we may mail the information packet.
Tools For SchoolsWe request information from the user on our Tools For School card link page. This information is used to link a user's Advantage Card with a chosen school. The information collected is used for processing the request and confirmation.
Ask LeahWe request information from the user on our Ask Leah page. This information is used so that Leah may respond directly to the user for clarification, questions, or confirmation.
Weekly AdsWhen you pick a preferred store, we use a cookie to store which state you selected to make repeated visits easier. We do not share this information.
CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. How to delete cookies in Internet Explorer.
If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.
This website employs Google Analytics, a web-analysis tool from Google Inc. ("Google") that enables us to optimize our Services for you. Google Analytics uses cookies that track your preferences during your visit to our website. This allows us to simplify navigation, for example, thereby helping us to make the site more user-friendly. The information that is generated in this process (including the IP address) is anonymized, making personal identification impossible. An evaluation for reporting purposes is carried out only after the anonymization process. The data, generated by this Cookie are usually transferred and stored on a server in the USA. As a user of our website, you always have the option of disabling cookies in your browser settings. Most browsers allow cookies as a default setting. Should you change this setting, this may disrupt certain functions of our websites. Furthermore, you can prevent Google's acquisition and processing of the information that is generated by the cookie and concerns your activity on the website (including your IP address) by downloading and installing a browser plug-in. The actual link to the tool is: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de
Further information on the terms of use and the privacy options of Google are available on:http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html
Log FilesLike most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Communications from the Site
Customer ServiceWe communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
Order ProcessingWhen users place orders with us, contact us for information, or contact us to leave comments, they may receive automatic responses via email generated by our server, acknowledging their submission.
Sharing
Legal DisclaimerThough we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. Specifically, we disclose aggregate information about the numbers of visitors to our site, frequency of visits, and usage of various parts of the site.
These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties, except when required by law.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Ingles Markets, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email and by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.Last modified December, 2018
